Guide to the Tangren Alexander papers Coll 746
University of Oregon Libraries, Special Collections and University Archives
- Writings, circa 1950-2020, undated; 2.
  - Article and short story length, 1976-2016, undated; 2.2.
    - "Sex and Death, reading at Ni Aodagain's celebration of women's writing in honor of Tee Corinne", circa 2006 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - "Six Meditations on Deborah Kerr", after 1999 June 8 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - "Sophie Brahe", circa 1994 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - "Sophie's Wind, Dreams of the Goddess", 2001 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - "Subud article", 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - "Summer Solstice 1985" (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Tea and Sympathy, draft, circa 2001 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - "Tee's last day", 2006 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - "Tenderly: Remembering Deborah Kerr as printed in Sophie's Wind", undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - A Theory of Art, Tangren Pearl Time'sChild and Tee A. Corinne, booklets, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - "Things that go in A Different 1984, part 2" (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - "Valentine's Morning 2:00 AM from The Auto Biography of Deborah Carr", 1980 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - "Vision Questing Along I-5", circa 1977, undated (Box 6, Folder 35-36)
    - "Vision Questing Along I-5, this is really a spoken work", 1977 Spring (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - "What Dolls Do", undated (Box 6, Folder 38-39)
    - "What Dolls Do," "Magic Tricks and Tricksters", undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - "What Dolls Do," "Marcella, Feminism, Dolls, unfinished philosophical writing", undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - "Why The Nutcracker?", undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - "Winter Term Musings on the History/Herstory of Western Philosophy", 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 44-45)
    - "Winter Term Musings on the History/Herstory of Western Philosophy," "version to read", 1998 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - The Womanly Art of Teaching Ethics, circa 1980s - 1991 (Box 6, Folder 47-49)
    - "The Womanly Art of Teaching Ethics, typeset originals and copies", 1987-1991 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - "WomanSpirit writings", circa 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - "Women in World History," "Yorkin Press", 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - "Women's music", 1976 (Box 6, Folder 53-54)
    - Women's music, "letters from publishers", 1976 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Women's music, "MCHM concert: article, notes", 1976 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - "Writing about building", 2007 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - "Writings from A Different 1984" (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - "2:00 AM Valentine's Morning as article", 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - "2:00 AM Valentine's Morning, from The Auto Biography of Deborah Carr", 1980 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Poetry and music, circa 1974-1998, undated; 2.3.
    Related material can be found in series 4. Events, workshops, and conferences.
    - "Joe / Schrodinger's cat poems", undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - "Juno", undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - "Kali Lullaby", 1982 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - "The Omniscient Voice," "Onomatopoeia", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - "Poetry", circa 1974-1983 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - "Small pieces, poetry for magic and philosophy", undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - "Sonnet, graphics reference", circa 1987 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - "Things I could read", undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - "Vision Quest poetry", undated (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - We'moon, submission, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - The Women's Review of Books, submission, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Notes and fragments, circa 1950-2020, undated; 2.4.
    Related material can be found throughout Series 2. Writings.
    - "The adventure, notes", undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - "The alpha workshop days", undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - "Barbies: overview of work", undated (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - "The blanks fill in", circa 1970s (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - "Death", circa 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - "Deborah Kerr", circa 2001 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - "Deborah Kerr for SWIP", circa 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - "Deborah Kerr writings from the '50s", 1950s (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - "Dianne", undated (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Draft fragments, circa 1980s (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - "Dream Wife, etc., writings", undated (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - "Dreams", undated (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - "Dressing Like Men", circa 1985 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - "Ethics papers topics and notes", undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "The Extraterrestrial", undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "First writing", 1976 January (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Flying Dreams", circa 1999 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fragments, circa 1970s (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "The Girl Next Door", 1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Holy Weed article", undate (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - "How to be a writer", undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - "The Interior Woman", circa 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - "Lecture notes - January 1980, originals of article", 1980 January (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - "Low Echoes", undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - "New writing", 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Notes, 2019-2020 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - "Note for Ostensive Definitions", 1977 April 14 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - "Notes on The Boxed Set", undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - "Old drafts, etc.", undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - "Other recent writing on Dianne", undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - "Possible Ursula Le Guin letter "paper" piece", circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - "Recent Deborah history / writing", 2004 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - "Selene", 1977 Spring (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "Tarot Party / Book: Celebrating Ourselves / Mother / Daughter Evening", undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - "Things to go in your journals as they're completed", 1982 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - "Timed 10-minute writing", 1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Vision Quest material, circa 1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - "Vision Quest prose", undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - "Vision Quest tapes, transcriptions", undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - "The Wedding", 1986 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - "A Woman Appeared to Me", 1976 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - "Writing The Natural Way", undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - "Writing - plans, ideas", undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - "Writings on Grief / Jessie", 1995 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - "Yantras review (possible)", undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Chronological files, 1974-2018; 2.5.
    Related material can be found throughout the collection.
    - 1974-2018 (Box 7, Folder 33-46)
  - Material about publishing, circa 1978-2010, undated; 2.6.
    - "Copyright / Public Domain", 2009 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Lettering, printing material, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - "Places to publish / calls for material", circa 1978-1990 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - "Printing and photocopying information", undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - "Publishers / calls for material", circa 1983-1987 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - "Publishing Books Group", 2010 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - "Publishing re Deborah Kerr", 2007 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Teaching material, circa 1988-2001, undated; 3.
  Series 3. Teaching material is arranged alphabetically by file title.
  The teaching material series contains course materials, Northwest Women's Studies Association directories, a poster, and office artifacts from Alexander's time as a philosophy and women's studies professor.
  Material related to presentations and workshops led by Alexander at academic conferences and events can be found in Series 4. Events, workshops, and conferences.
  - Northwest Women's Studies Association directories, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Office artifacts, nameplates, volvelle, undated (Box 20)
  - "Philosophy and Ursula Le Guin course", 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - "Teaching Shelley's class, overview of feminism, philosophy, me", circa 1990s (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - "Ursula Le Guin as a philosopher", circa 1988-1996 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - "Women's Studies doll poster", 2001 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Events, workshops, and conferences, circa 1977-2020, undated; 4.
  Series 4. Events, workshops, and conferences is arranged alphabetically by file title.
  The events, workshops, and conferences series contains notes, writings, flyers, correspondence, and ephemera from workshops, conferences, readings, and other events that Alexander participated in or attended. This series includes drafts of Alexander's writings that were read or presented at events and gatherings.
  - "A and L reading", 1999 November (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - "Being a Visiting Dyke, Shelly's class", 1998 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - "Conference on Gender and Culture", 2002 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - "Contacts for Readings", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - "Engendering Rationalities Conference", 1997 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - "Eugene reading", 1990 April (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - "Faculty Lecture program", 1993 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - "Flight of the Mind application", 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - "Gender studies symposium," call for papers, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - "Giving The Body It's Due", 1979-1989 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - "Glide writing workshop", 2012 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - "History of Philosophy writings for Society for Women in Philosophy meeting", 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "Illahe reading", 2009 May (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "A Kademe is a Grove of Trees," Southern Oregon Women's Writer Group presentation at Society for Women in Philosophy meeting, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - "Kristina talk, notes", 1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Lavender Life Support Conference, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Lewis and Clark College Gender Studies Symposium, Tea and Sympathy, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "May 2, 2003 presentation" (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - "November 2 reading", 2002 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "NWWSA conference, Portland reading", 1988 October (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "Reading Deborah Kerr material, publishing", circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - "Reading at The Salon of the Muses sonnet", undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - "Reading, Sandra's Tearoom", undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Readings with Hannah", circa 1977-1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - "Selling Non-Fiction and Fiction Workshop", circa 1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Society for Women in Philosophy, "Presentation / ideas / me", 1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Southern Oregon Women Writers' Group events, ephemera, 2016, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Southern Oregon Women Writers' Group presents: 14 Years of Writing: A Celebration", 1995 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - "Southern Oregon Writers' Group Reading Fall '03 gathering", 2003 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - "Tee Corinne Memorial, speech, Tee's Remembering as a Way of Life", 2006 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - "Tee reading October '08", 2008 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - "Ursula Le Guin Class on Publishing", 1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - "The Womanly Art of Teaching Ethics," poster, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - "A WomanSpirit Evening", 1980s (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Women in Print Conference, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - "Women's History Month", 2020 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - "Writers' Group Reading, Eugene", 1989 April (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - "Writers' Group Reading, Tee celebration in Eugene", 2008 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - "Writers' Group 10th Anniversary Reading", 1991 April (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - "Writing on Tee's death and reading on that", circa 2006 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - "Written for Ursula Le Guin workshop", circa 1990s (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Doll photography, circa 1990-2012, undated; 5.
  Series 5. Doll photography is arranged in its original order.
  The doll photography series contains photographic prints, slides, and negatives from doll photography projects. This series also includes albums, homemade books, scripts, notes, writings, and ephemera related to doll photography. A significant portion of the material is related to the "Selene" project.
  - "Speaking Through Barbie," in Jefferson Monthly, 2000 September (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - "Prints of Dolls", 2010 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - "The Fairygodmother's Gift", 1995 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - "Selene," notes, circa 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - "Selene," script, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - "Selene" scripts, "Kira" script, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - "What Dolls Do Exhibit comments", 2012 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - "The Mysterious Book", undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - "Documentation on Dolls", 2007 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Mounted prints, undated (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
  - "Selene" prints, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 1-17)
  - "Dolls," prints, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - "A Walk in the Woods, Family Adventures II," photo album, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - "Selene" slides, circa 1990s (Box 19, Slide box 1-2)
  - "Sunshine girls at ocean, Selene and moon", circa 1990s (Box 19, Slide box 2)
  - "The Prom, extras", circa 1990s (Box 19, Slide box 2)
  - "Women and Philosophy poster", circa 1990s (Box 19, Slide box 2)
  - "Raggedy's face, extras", circa 1990s (Box 19, Slide box 2)
  - "FGM's gift, extra", 1997 (Box 19, Slide box 2)
- Personal papers, circa 1943-2023, undated; 6.
  Series 6. Personal papers is arranged in five subseries:
  6.1. Biographical material, circa 1943-2023, undated
  6.2. Journals, circa 1953-2020
  6.3. Student material, 1948-1989
  6.4. Ephemera, circa 1950-2020, undated
  6.5. Photographs, circa 1950-2010, undated
  The personal papers series contains material related to Alexander's personal life. This series includes biographical material, journals, student material, ephemera, and photographs.
  The biographical material subseries contains autobiographies, transcripts of interviews with Alexander, astrological charts, and a capture of Alexander's personal website.
  The journals subseries contains handwritten personal journals and diaries, as well as printouts of typed versions of select handwritten journals. Some journals contain inserted correspondence, notes, ephemera, and photographs.
  The student material subseries contains material from Alexander's time as a student, spanning elementary school to graduate school, as well as continuing education classes. This subseries includes notes, report cards, application materials, writings, correspondence, and a dissertation.
  The ephemera subseries contains ephemera related to Alexander's personal life, including notes, printouts, flyers, programs, posters, directories, and Deborah Kerr materials.
  The photographs subseries contains photographic prints, negatives, and slides. The photographs are predominantly personal snapshots of Alexander and her friends. The subseries includes photographs taken by Tee Corinne and Ruth Mountaingrove.
  - Biographical material, circa 1943-2023, undated; 6.1.
    - "Astrology, Tangren's charts", undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - "Bios, etc.", 1989 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - "Heather Burmeister interview of me", 2011-2012 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - "Interview with Tangren Alexander by Jennifer Almquist", 2004 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - "Karen Dudenhoeffer interview of me", 1997 (Restricted box 21, Folder 4)
      Access to the folder ""Karen Dudenhoeffer interview of me," 1997" is closed until 2072 due to the presence of student records of a third-party individual.
    - Tangren Alexander website capture, 2023; Coll746_do001; 151 megabyte(s)
    - "Tangren Time Line", circa 1943-1994 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Journals, circa 1953-2020; 6.2.
    The journals subseries contains handwritten personal journals and diaries, as well as print-outs of typed versions of select handwritten journals. Some journals contain inserted correspondence, notes, ephemera, and photographs. Alexander titled several of her journals and later published them.
    - Journals, circa 1953-2020 (Box 11, Folder 27-36, Box 12, Folder 1-17, Box 13, Box 14, Folder 1-15, Box 15)
    - Typed journals, 1976-1991 (Box 16, Folder 1-30)
  - Student material, 1948-1989; 6.3.
    - Elementary school report cards, 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Reed College, application material, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Writings, letters, school work, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - "College class notes", 1958-1961 (Box 8, Folder 48-50)
    - "June 11, Tuesday", circa 1958-1962 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Notebook, circa 1958-1962 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Norman Malcolm and Dreaming and Nonsense, bound dissertation, 1975 (Box 8, Volume 53)
    - Norman Malcolm correspondence about dissertation, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - "Physics 310", 1982-1989 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Ephemera, circa 1950-2020, undated; 6.4.
    - "Addresses, WomanSource", 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - "Addresses, women in print, feminist writers, guild, etc.", 1984-1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - "Amazon tarot cards owned by Tangren Alexander, several images by local women photographers", undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - "Astrological charts", 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - "Beach St. Bulletin Board", circa 1973-1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - "Birthday party", circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - "Chester Fitch, Final account and petition for decree of final distribution", 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - "Copies of work sent and to send (recap of Acts and Intention)", 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - "Deborah Kerr Database", 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - "Deborah Kerr on the internet," printouts, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - "Deborah Kerr material from Deborah", circa 1950s - 1980s (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - "Desk miscellany, 1540 Jefferson St.", circa 1971-1976 (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
    - Flyers, programs, 2002-2018, undated (Box 9, Folder 13-18)
    - "General Jinjur", undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Gertrude's Cafe poster, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - "Goes in current journal", 1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - "Grants, etc.", 1982 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - "Graphics", undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - "Jean's Tribute to Dad, memorial", undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - "Jumpoff Joe 'n Seymour", 1983-1992 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - "Libré", 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - "My Ozmazon poster", 1976 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - "My retirement dance," flyer, correspondence, photographs, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - "My retirement dance, poster making", 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - "My 70th birthday speech", circa 2010 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Notes, circa 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - "Old Lesbian Oral Herstory Project", 2013 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Oregon Literary Directory, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - "Pages for Athena", 2013 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - "Poster originals, various", undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - "Publicity Sources, events", 1983 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - "Raggedy Ann postcard, Have a nice day postcard", undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - "Sandra, astrology", 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Scrapbook, The National Thespian Society member card, circa 1950s (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - "Signs, posters, invitations", circa 1976 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - "Subud writers", 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - "Talk with Narda Verbieren, Dianne's sister", 2005 May (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - "Tee Corinne's death," notes, correspondence, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - "Verbieren, Dianne and Narda", 2000s (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - "Woman's community ephemera", 1980-2005 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - WomanSource Rising buttons, Society for Women in Philosophy button, 2005, undated (Box 20)
    - "WomanSpirit microforms", 2020 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - "WomanSpirit webpage", circa 1999 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - "Writing", 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - "50th birthday", circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Photographs, circa 1950-2010, undated; 6.5.
    - "Black and white photos of Tee's house by Tangren Alexander from the '80s?", circa 1980s (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Camp memory book, scrapbook, circa 1950-1959 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - "Canada trip, summer '10, photos by sherry", 2010 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Corinne, Tee, "Miscellaneous Images of Tee Corinne with Tangren Alexander and/or taken by Tee Corinne", undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - "Dianne, Sandra, Ruth, Tangren", undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - "Hannah and me, photographed by Ruth Mountaingrove", 1985 June (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - "In the park", circa 2000s (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - "Karen / me", 2001, undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Katie Niles photographs, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - "Me - portraits and self-portraits, mostly from age 50", 1990 (Box 19, Slide box 3)
    - "Miscellaneous images, Tangren Alexander", undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - "My living room, kitchen, bedroom, early nineties or late 80s", circa 1985-1995 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - "Photographs by Hawk Madrone", 2001 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - "Photos by Madrone of me working on Tea and Sympathy writing", 2001 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - "Pictures from book on Crete", undated (Box 19, Slide box 3)
    - "Pictures of Butterfly", circa 1977 (Box 19, Slide box 3)
    - "Pictures of Butterfly and me (private), give to Butterfly", circa 1977 (Box 19, Slide box 3)
    - Portrait by Ruth Mountaingrove, undated (Box 17, Folder 11, Box 18, Folder 29)
    - "Ruth and Jean's cabin at Wolf Creek, taken by Ruth Moutnaingrove, 200 Ashland loop road, construction pictures - wiring", circa 1978 (Box 19, Slide box 3)
    - "Sandra and Tangren", 1987 April (Box 19, Slide box 3)
    - "Sappho sculpture by or with Tangren", undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - "Sherry O'Sullivan", 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - "Sherry O'Sullivan photos xeroxed", undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - "Sherry's rings, my breasts, taken by Tee Corinne," prints, negatives, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - "Solarized photos of me by Tee", 2005 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - "Taken by Ruth Mountaingrove", undated (Box 19, Slide box 3)
    - "Tangren pictures", 1990s-2000s (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - "Tarot series with Tangren, Tee Corinne, and others", undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - "Tee Corinne photos", 2006 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - "Tee Corinne 8/26/06", 2006 August 26 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - "Tee Corinne's photo of Tangren", circa 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - "Tee's photos of me", undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Unidentified print, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Unidentified project, negatives, slides, prints, undated (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - "Writers' Group photos by Tee", 2005 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - "Writer's Group reading, spring, Dot and John Fisher-Smith's house in Ashland", 2001 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Work by others, 1916-2021, undated; 7.
  Series 7. Work by others is arranged in three subseries:
  7.1. Southern Oregon Women Writers' Group, 1983-2021, undated
  7.2. Tee Corinne material, circa 1968-2008, undated
  7.3. Collected writings and clippings, 1916-2020, undated
  The work by others series contains published and unpublished writings, art, and audiovisual materials collected by Alexander. This series includes Southern Oregon Women Writers' Group material, Tee Corinne material, and collected writings and clippings.
  The Southern Oregon Women Writers' Group subseries contains material created by and about the Southern Oregon Women Writers' Group, Gourmet Eating Society, and Chorus. The subseries includes published and unpublished writings and two VHS tapes from the group's 2003 Fall Gathering.
  The Tee Corinne material subseries contains material created by and about American photographer, artist, and writer Tee A. Corinne. The subseries includes manuscripts, publications, artwork, drawings, and a VHS tape of Gryphon: Another Colored Drag Queen.
  The collected writings and clippings subseries contains publications, writings, and clippings collected by Alexander. The subseries includes manuscripts, articles, magazines, newsletters, and newspapers, such as WomanSource Rising News.
  - Southern Oregon Women Writers' Group, 1983-2021, undated; 7.1.
    Material related to the Southern Oregon Women Writers' Group, Gourmet Eating Society, and Chorus may also be found in Series 2. Writings and Series 4. Events, workshops, and conferences.
    - Astrological birth mandala for Southern Oregon Women Writers' Group, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Emailed writings, 2016-2021 (Box 9, Folder 67)